A Guide to the The Photographic Archive of Fairfax County, Virginia - The Slide Collection, 1961-1998
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Kalorama Springs (Tricketts), Colvin Run, 1968; Box 5: TRIC-2
- Tysons Corner Shoppping Center, 1970; Box 5: TSYO-1
- Tysons Corner Shoppping Center, 1970; Box 5: TSYO-2
- Tysons Corner Shoppping Center, 1970; Box 5: TSYO-3
- Tysons Corner Shoppping Center, 1970; Box 5: TSYO-4
- Tysons Corner Crossroads c. 1935 (photo by S.R. Pearson), Undated; Box 5: TYSO-10 (1 of 2)
- Tysons Corner Crossroads c. 1935 (photo by S.R. Pearson), Undated; Box 5: TYSO-10 (2 of 2)
- Tysons Corner, Construction of Route 123 overpass, 1964 (photo by Donie Rieger), Undated; Box 5: TYSO-13
- Tysons Corner, Cross Roads Market, 1956 (photo by Homer Heller), Undated; Box 5: TYSO-48
- Tysons Corner, View northwest from the northwest corner of Chain Bridge Road and Old Courthouse Road, 1972 (photo by Nan Netherton), Undated; Box 5: TYSO-63
- Tysons Corner, View north from the northwest corner of Chain Bridge Road and Old Courthouse Road, 1972 (photo by Nan Netherton), Undated; Box 5: TYSO-64
- Tysons Corner, Oblique view looking east at the Dulles Toll Road, Mall at bottom center, 1968 (photo by Blue Ridge Aerial Surveys), Undated; Box 5: TYSO-AER-6
- Vienna Train Station, 1968; Box 5: VIEN-RS-1
- Vienna Train Station, 1968; Box 5: VIEN-RS-2 (1 of 2)
- Vienna Train Station, 1968; Box 5: VIEN-RS-2 (2 of 2)
- Vienna Presbyterian Church, 1968; Box 5: VIEN-PC-1
- Vienna Presbyterian Church, 1968; Box 5: VIEN-PC-2
- Wakefield Chapel, 1966 January 8; Box 5: WAKE-1
- Wakefield Chapel, 1966 January 8; Box 5: WAKE-2 (1 of 2)
- Wakefield Chapel, 1966 January 8; Box 5: WAKE-2 (2 of 2)
- Wakefield Chapel, Undated; Box 5: WAKE-3
- Wakefield Chapel, John Locke, Edward Youngblood and Gene Cave, 1966 January 8; Box 5: WAKE-4
- Wakefield Chapel, Rev. Winfree and Carl Olson, 1966 January 8; Box 5: WAKE-5
- Wakefield Chapel, Rev. Winfree and Carl Olson, 1966 January 8; Box 5: WAKE-6
- Wakefield Chapel, 1968; Box 5: WAKE-7
- Wakefield Chapel, 1968; Box 5: WAKE-8
- Wakefield Chapel, 1968; Box 5: WAKE-9
- Wakefield Chapel, 1968; Box 5: WAKE-10
- Wakefield Chapel, 1968; Box 5: WAKE-11 (1 of 2)
- Wakefield Chapel, 1968; Box 5: WAKE-11 (2 of 2)
- Wakefield Chapel, 1968; Box 5: WAKE-12
- Wakefield Chapel, 1968; Box 5: WAKE-13
- Wakefield Chapel, 1968; Box 5: WAKE-14
- Wakefield Chapel, 1968; Box 5: WAKE-15
- Wakefield Chapel, 1968; Box 5: WAKE-16
- Wakefield Chapel, 1968; Box 5: WAKE-17
- Wake Robin, Roberts Road, Fairfax City, 1976; Box 5: WAKE-R-1
- Wanley (photo by E. Breitenbach), Undated; Box 5: WALN-1
- Walney, 1968; Box 5: WALN-2
- Walney, "Cheese Factory", Spring House (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: WALN-3
- Walney, "Cheese Factory", Spring House (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: WALN-4
- Walney, "Cheese Factory", Spring House (photo by E. Breitenbach), 1967; Box 5: WALN-5
- Walnut Hill, Annandale Road, 1972; Box 5: WALN-H-1 (1 of 3)
- Walnut Hill, Annandale Road, 1972; Box 5: WALN-H-1 (3 of 3)
- Martha Washington's Will, Undated; Box 5: WASH-W
- Fairfax County Weights and Measures, 1744, housed in Masonic Memorial museum, Alexandria, VA, (photo by Anthony Hathaway), 1974; Box 5: WEIG-1
- Wolftrap, Filene Center, Undated; Box 5: WOLF-FC-1
- Wolftrap, Filene Center, 1975; Box 5: WOLF-FC-2
- Wolftrap, Filene Center Stage, International Child Day, 1974; Box 5: WOLF-FC-3
- Wolftrap, Plantation, Mrs. Shouse, 1972; Box 5: WOLF-SH-1 (1 of 2)
- Wolftrap, Plantation, Mrs. Shouse, 1972; Box 5: WOLF-SH-1 (2 of 2)
- Woodlawn Friend's Meeting House, 1968; Box 5: WOOD-FMH-1
- Woodlawn Friend's Meeting House, 1968; Box 5: WOOD-FMH-2
- Woodlawn Friend's Meeting House, 1968; Box 5: WOOD-FMH-3
- Woodlawn Plantation, Mount Vernon, Undated; Box 5: WOOD-P-1 (2 of 2)
- Woodlawn Plantation, Mount Vernon, Carriage Entrance, Undated; Box 5: WOOD-P-2 (2 of 3)
- Woodlawn Plantation, Mount Vernon, Carriage Entrance, Undated; Box 5: WOOD-P-2 (3 of 3)
- Woodlawn Plantation, Mount Vernon, Playroom, 1975; Box 5: WOOD-P-3 (1 of 2)
- Woodlawn Plantation, Mount Vernon, Playroom, 1975; Box 5: WOOD-P-3 (2 of 2)
- Woodlawn Plantation, Mount Vernon, Playroom, Undated; Box 5: WOOD-P-4 (1 of 2)
- Woodlawn Plantation, Mount Vernon, Playroom, Undated; Box 5: WOOD P-4 (2 of 2)